picture?
え?
I haven't reflected on it at all.
全然反省してないじゃん
picture?
え?
No, I reflected on it.
いや、反省したよ
Pants are a different matter.
パンツは別物だよ
I told you to stop.
やめてって言ったじゃん
No pants?
パンツダメ?
No.
ダメ
I really want it to stop.
普通に本当にやめてほしい
Do you really want it to stop?
普通に本当にやめてほしい?
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌なんだ
Sorry, I'll clean it up.
ごめん、片付けるから
Put away your pants.
パンツ片付ける
I'll open my pants and put them on.
パンツ開きはめるからさ
Show me something again.
もう一回何か見せてくれ
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
I wanted to see something.
何か見たくて
I saw it just now.
さっき見たじゃん
Like take a closer look.
もっとじっくりみたいに
Like taking a closer look.
も っとじっくりみたいに
I don't like it, it's just embarrassing.
嫌だ、普通に恥ずかしいし
Okay, show me.
いいじゃん、見せてよ
please.
お願い
Come here.
こっち来てさ
Show me your eyes properly.
ちゃんと目を見せてよ
That's good.
いいよね
We're already getting along.
もう仲乗りちゃうもんね
It's still a little suspicious though.
まだちょっと怪しいけどね
Suspicious?
怪 しい?
Come over there.
そこへ手前に来てさ
Living from below?
下から生きる?
Pick it up from below?
下から拾い入れる?
From below?
下から?
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Yes, it's over.
はい、終わり
That's no good.
ダメだね
I'll look at your pants.
パンツ見るよ
Get on your knees and face me.
膝立ちしてこっち向いて
beside your hand
手横に
do.
して
Do it like this again.
もう 一回こうやってさ
Yeah.
うん